Yulin Li

13923324995 | 853679482@qq.com Zhongshan, Guangdong https://qq853679482.wixsite.com/yulinli



EDUCATION

University of Melbourne Aug 2022

Master of Management (finance)

Melbourne

I started to learn about finance, economics, accounting and statistics in 2022.

University of Melbourne

Bachelor of Design (Architecture & Construction)

Feb 2018 - Jul 2022 Melbourne

Relevant courses:

architectural history, digital design, construction design, landscape design, public building design, building environment system, Construction management, and principles of business law.

SKILLS LIST

Proficient in three-dimensional modelling software Rhino+Grasshopper. Can generate rendering images through Enscape, Lumion, Twinmotion and other software.

Proficient in using Adobe software such as Ai, Id, Ps and other software.

Proficient in using Office software.

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Credohus Architects Nov 2020 - Feb 2021

Architect intern Guangzhou

Participate in the whole process of renovation of a restaurant in Yunfu Luoding, and complete the process of making three-dimensional models, facade design, interior design, lighting design and construction drawing. Change the plan according to the requirements of the customer and the designer, and finally complete the project landing.

Participate in and assist the designer to complete the surveying and mapping of a teaching building of the Guangzhou Academy of Fine Arts.

Participate in the product design of wooden children's furniture.

PROJECT EXPERIENCE

Jacques Rougerie Foundation International Architecture Competition

May 2021 - Aug 2021

Contact and organize 6 teammates from Malaysia, India, China Hong Kong and mainland China to participate in the Jacques Rougerie Foundation International Architecture Competition. Responsible for coordinating tasks, arranging processes, organizing meetings and other work, and finally entering the finals and being nominated.

HONORS & AWARDS

2020 works are exhibited in the school exhibition MSDx.

2020

2021 works are exhibited in the school exhibition MSDx. Participated in the international design competition and Jacques Rougerie Foundation International Architecture Competition and being nominated

2021

Personal skills

- Languages: Mandarin (mother tongue), Cantonese (mother tongue), English (fluent)
- Interests: Fitness, basketball, swimming

SUMMARY

Have good communication and coordination ability, be good at adapting to the new environment quickly; have strong self-study ability, can quickly learn knowledge in new fields; strong pressure resistance.

李钰林

13923324995 | 853679482@qq.com | 广东中山 https://qq853679482.wixsite.com/yulinli 在读



❷ 教育经历

墨尔本大学 2022年08月 - 2024年07月

2022年开始学习相关金融,经济,会计与统计相关内容

墨尔本大学 2018年02月 - 2022年07月

建筑设计及建造 本科 墨尔本

相关课程:

建筑史,数字化设计,施工设计,景观设计,公共建筑设计,建筑环境系统,工程管理,商法原理。

❷ 专业技能

熟练掌握三维建模软件Rhino + Grasshopper. 能通过Enscape, Lumion, Twinmotion等软件生成渲染图。

熟练使用Adobe旗下的软件如Ai, Id, Ps等软件。

熟练使用Office软件。

母 实习经历

合作舍建筑事务所 2020年11月 - 2021年02月

建筑实习生

参与云浮罗定某餐厅改造全过程,完成包括三维模型制作,外立面设计,室内设计,灯光设计及施工图绘制过程。根据甲方与设计师需求更改方案最终完成项目落地。

参与并协助设计师完成广州美术学院一教学楼的测绘。

参与木制儿童家具的产品设计。

😝 项目经历

Jacques Rougerie Foundation International Architecture Competition

2021年05月 - 2021年08月

联系与组织来自马来西亚,印度,中国香港,中国大陆的6位队友参加Jacques Rougerie Foundation International Architecture Competition。负责协调任务,安排进程,组织会议等工作,最终进入决赛并获得提名。

♥ 荣誉奖项

2020 作品在学校展览MSDx中展出。

2020

2021 作品在学校展览MSDx中展出。 2021年参加国际设计竞赛Jacques Rougerie Foundation International Architecture Competition进入决赛提名

2021

母 个人技能

● **语言:** 普通话(母语),粤语(母语),英语(流利)

• 兴趣爱好: 健身,篮球,游泳

🗗 个人总结

拥有良好的沟通和协调能力,善于应变,能够快速适应新环境;

拥有较强的自学能力,能快速学习新领域的知识;

抗压能力较强。